homeschool-life.com 2018-12-14

# Homeschool-Life.com :: Homeschool Group and Co-op Websites | Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

**Your privacy and the privacy of your group is imperative to us!**

**Our Commitment to Privacy.** We value your privacy. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and our terms of service are at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect.** This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Homeschool-Life.com website. On some interactive pages, such as when you request membership into your respective homeschool group, you will be prompted for information. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email Address & Preferences
  * Phone Number
  * Children Information (you have the choice to decline)

**The Way We Use Information.** We use the information you provide about yourself during membership registration only for its intended purpose—to complete your registration into your respective homeschool group. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete the membership registration. 

We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to what is described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Our Commitment to Data Security.** To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy.** Protecting the privacy of the very young is of utmost importance. For that reason, we have made the collection and maintenance of information at our website optional for those whom we know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under age 13. Collecting children’s information is solely the responsibility of the website administrator for each respective homeschool group.

**How can you Access or Correct Your Information?** You, and each member of your group, can access and maintain all of your personally identifiable information that we collect online by using your secure login. During the registration process you, and each member of your group, will create your own login and password. This secure login gives you access to your personal profile, which is maintained by you. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by updating that information yourself; each member has access to update their own family information.

**How to Contact Us.** Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 720-755-0257 or send us an email at [info@homeschool-life.com](mailto:info@homeschool-life.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Question%2FConcern).

Click on Sample Registration to see what type of information could be collected during registration:
